Hi, and so to last time, I want to show you what is the data privacy and security of the
VIN sort of code the data.
So I will go through main points of this documentation and if you want to read more or
search more, you can find this link in the resources for this lesson and I also shared
the link for privacy policy page.
So there is a term, zero data retention in VIN sort, it means that your code or code like
you sent never saved on the servers and can be only processed in memory which can be
stored in a few minutes or some number of hours.
So I'll let quickly search, I especially highlighted some key moments with the green
color, they just different colors because they keep together.
Because moments that any team or enterprise plan, so all inputs and outputs for this
request follow zero data retention policy by default.
So if you are enterprise plan, a team plan, you shouldn't care about any tall goals
in your settings, it's enabled by default.
And if you're an individual plan like three or problem, you have an optional toggle as
yes in the settings.
So when you install your application, your VIN sort for the data, you need to go to
settings and disable it and this way you will enable zero data retention mode and your data
1% or VIN sort of one between it on them.
So let go to the next key points, you can see, so VIN of each of these requests like some
magenta experience or some autocomplete, super complete or tap the jump features with
the VIN sort, also with the command, it's in line shot for terminal and code the guitar, and
some real time, the client machine sends a combination of the context, I just sort of
on snippets of code, recent actions, so file names, sometimes conversation history, some
users, specified signals, like rules, memories, etc.
But most single requests contain the entire code base or really large portions of codes
or more.
As it tells, they send it to the server to compute yet to process it, but not receiving
a single request within the entire code base, so they like sent only small parts and needed
for execute the particular request.
You also can see that there is some usage analytics, but it's not about the code data,
it's only about some usage metadata, and they log it to BigQuery on their servers.
So it's about that they can save some information here with features you run, so how many
times you run, etc, there's some metadata.
Also, if an individual plan without zero data retention mode, if you have not enabled the
struggle, thumb logs may contain cod snippets and user, so this information can be stored,
so just be aware of it.
Okay, I'll let go next, there is another, you can use different features, like different
features from VensorFlow, like deployment plans, the web search, etc.
And there are a lot of providers, like Google Cloud providers, AWS, OpenAI for some models
and proper pick and other providers, and of course there is a bank API, so if you use
a bank API, the VensorFlow doesn't have zero data retention policy agreement with BIMP,
and for example, so it can contain some user inputs, some conversation history, potentially
there's some cod data, so please be aware if you're on enterprise, so you can disable
this bank API from settings, okay, I'll let go next, what else, so we have the zero data
retention mode, guarantees that cod or cod driver data is never serialized or stored in
a plaintext at our servers or by subprocessors, so also zero data retention mode is a default
or any user of a team or enterprise plan and can be enabled by individual from the
profile page, so you will just need to open the VensorFlow, go to settings and enable the
start though if you're on individual plan, also the cod data is still visible to servers in memory,
for the YF time of the request, because they need processes information, and you see some
time as might exist for someone to preload in order to minutess minutes of hours for
some replication, also the cod data submitted by zero data retention mode users will
never be trained on, this is important option that if you enable this total VensorFlow
one train on your data, or one train their models, this is the main key points, so that
you understand what is the security and data privacy or source that is already transparent
with the users who use it and so I hope this information was really useful to you, and
see you in the next lesson.